<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Works on Katsufumi Matsui</title>
    <link>http://karadaharu.org/katsufumi/works/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Works on Katsufumi Matsui</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2016 23:26:19 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://karadaharu.org/katsufumi/works/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>some</title>
      <link>http://karadaharu.org/katsufumi/works/some/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2016 23:26:19 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://karadaharu.org/katsufumi/works/some/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>agic</title>
      <link>http://karadaharu.org/katsufumi/works/agic/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2016 22:27:45 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://karadaharu.org/katsufumi/works/agic/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;AgIC Erasable Circuit Marker Promotion Video&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Producer/Director Katsufumi Matsui
Director of Photography/Editor Shinsuke Yasui
Music Yoshihito Nakanishi
Designer Yoshihito Nakanishi, Seico Okamoto, Natsuki Doi
Engineer Kazunori Ogasawara, Nobuhiro Sunada, Jotaro Shigeyama
Script Shinya Shimizu
Cast Natsuki Doi/Yoshihito Nakanishi/Seico Okamoto, Yoshihiro Kawahara, Allen Pan,
Shinya Shimizu, Yuki Nishida, Kazunori Ogasawara, Jotaro Shigeyamao&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world’s first eraser for conductive ink drawings.
Now anyone can make their own circuits on paper quickly and easily.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 360° Skyline Song</title>
      <link>http://karadaharu.org/katsufumi/works/item2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2016 22:05:35 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://karadaharu.org/katsufumi/works/item2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;video-container&#34;&gt;
&lt;iframe src=&#34;https://player.vimeo.com/video/90098467&#34; width=&#34;500&#34; height=&#34;281&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Katsufumi Matsui&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Technical cooperation
Kazunori Ogasawara
Seico Okamoto&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Special thanks to
Seiichiro Matsumura
Boyoung Kim
Tatsuya Ogusu
Toru Nakamoto
Kohei Morita&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;lsquo;The 360° Skyline Song&amp;rsquo; is an audio-visual installation work that makes sound waves
from the visual &amp;ldquo;boundary&amp;rdquo; between surrounding scenery and sky.
The visual data, made by recording the surrounding scenery with a video camera rotating an angle of 360 degrees,
are transformed into sound waves in real time by analyzing each camera frame.
By acquiring the color temperature and the atmospheric temperature there simultaneously,
&amp;lsquo;The 360° Skyline Song&amp;rsquo; improvises the expressive synthesis unique to the moment,
so they are live and impressive to the audience.
Both audio and visual data achieve the intuitive recognition of the transition of the boundary in sceneries.
This installation implies the instability of surroundings,
by interactively producing sound from changing surroundings and showing the captured movie.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boundary Synthesizer I</title>
      <link>http://karadaharu.org/katsufumi/works/item1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2016 21:29:11 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://karadaharu.org/katsufumi/works/item1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;video-container&#34;&gt;
&lt;iframe src=&#34;https://player.vimeo.com/video/114414871&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Katsufumi Matsui&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Technical cooperation
Seico Okamoto&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Boundary Synthesizer I is an interactive audio-visual installation work that makes sound waves
by analysis of the visual “boundary” of sceneries.Those sceneries come from various videos.
The computer vision system detects the boundary lines of sceneries, such as cityscapes, sea waves and fireworks, automatically.
This boundary line is extracted from the outline in each video frame and is directly transformed into the sound wave line.
Users can manipulate parameters by turning knobs and pushing switches of the interface as with typical musical synthesizers.
Thus, this installation is an audio-visual synthesizer in which the oscillator’s waveform is structured by the visual boundary.
This synthesizer has 2 oscillators – 2 video images are encoded simultaneously.
Users can enjoy playing with Boundary Synthesizer I by changing video inputs, controlling the frequency of ring modulation and pressing switches that modulate both video and sound.
Monotonous sounds are made from monotonous scenery; complex sounds are made from scenery with active movements,
for example sea waves and fireworks. Users can experience the intuitive connection of scenery and sound.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>